A Guide to the Institute of International Education records, Alumni and Historical Files, RG 1 FA1289
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Historical Files, 3
  - General - Special Projects Visiting Professors in U.S. - 1939-40 (Reel 21, Side 1, Index 12), Reel 21, Side 1, Index 12 (Reel 21)
  - General - Speicial Projects Lecturers - Descriptive List Mildred Adams' Desk Copy - 1940-41 (Reel 25, Side 1, Index 13), Reel 25, Side 1, Index 13 (Reel 25)
  - Special Projects Publicity - Lists for Lecturers - 1941 (Reel 21, Side 2, Index 14), Reel 21, Side 2, Index 14 (Reel 21)
  - General - Special Projects Lecturers - Curriculum Vitae to 1946 (Reel 25, Side 1, Index 14), Reel 25, Side 1, Index 14 (Reel 25)
  - Special Projects Terms for Lecturers - 1947-48 (Reel 21, Side 2, Index 15), Reel 21, Side 2, Index 15 (Reel 21)
  - General - Special Projects Lecturers - British-American Associates - 1947-50 (Reel 25, Side 1, Index 21), Reel 25, Side 1, Index 21 (Reel 25)
  - Special Projects Lecturer Material - Samples - 1947-50 (Reel 21, Side 2, Index 16), Reel 21, Side 2, Index 16 (Reel 21)
  - Special Projects Speakers Bureau Reports - 1948 (Reel 21, Side 2, Index 17), Reel 21, Side 2, Index 17 (Reel 21)
  - Special Projects Statistical Report of Lecturers in U.S. - 1919-1947 - 1948 (Reel 21, Side 2, Index 18), Reel 21, Side 2, Index 18 (Reel 21)
  - Special Projects - General - Immigration and Taxation Procedures or Professors and Lecturers - 1948-1950 (Reel 25, Side 1, Index 20), Reel 25, Side 1, Index 20 (Reel 25)
  - Special Projects - Report on Professors and Lecturers - 1948-50 (Reel 21, Side 2, Index 19), Reel 21, Side 2, Index 19 (Reel 21)
  - General - Special Projects - Publicity Mateial - I - Lecturers and Debaters - 1948-50 (Reel 20, Side 2, Index 15), Reel 20, Side 2, Index 15 (Reel 20)
  - General - Special Projects - Publicity Mateial - II - Lecturers and Debaters - 1949 (Reel 20, Side 2, Index 16), Reel 20, Side 2, Index 16 (Reel 20)
  - General - Special Projects - Publicity Mateial - III - Lecturers and Debaters - 1949 (Reel 20, Side 2, Index 17), Reel 20, Side 2, Index 17 (Reel 20)
  - General - Special Projects - Publicity Mateial - IV - Lecturers and Debaters - 1949 (Reel 20, Side 2, Index 18), Reel 20, Side 2, Index 18 (Reel 20)
  - General - Special Projects - Pamphlets on Lecturers and Debaters (1929-49) - 1949 (Reel 20, Side 2, Index 14), Reel 20, Side 2, Index 14 (Reel 20)
  - Special Projects - General - Summary of Prospective Lecturers for - 1949-50 (Reel 21, Side 2, Index 26), Reel 21, Side 2, Index 26 (Reel 21)
  - Special Projects - General - American Lecturers going Abroad - 1949-50 (Reel 21, Side 2, Index 27), Reel 21, Side 2, Index 27 (Reel 21)
  - Special Projects - Publicity - Commercial Lecture Bureaus - 1949-50 (Reel 21, Side 2, Index 20), Reel 21, Side 2, Index 20 (Reel 21)
  - General - Special Projects - Lecturers - 1949-52 (Reel 21, Side 1, Index 4), Reel 21, Side 1, Index 4 (Reel 21)
  - Special Projets - General - Lecturers for Summer Sessions - Replies to Form Letters - 1950 (Reel 21, Side 2, Index 31), Reel 21, Side 2, Index 31 (Reel 21)
  - General - Special Projects - Inquiries from Lecturers - A-K - 1951 (Reel 20, Side 2, Index 28), Reel 20, Side 2, Index 28 (Reel 20)
  - General - Special Projects - Inquiries from Lecturers - L-P - 1951 (Reel 20, Side 2, Index 29), Reel 20, Side 2, Index 29 (Reel 20)
  - General - Special Projects - Inquiries from Lecturers - R-Z - 1951 (Reel 20, Side 2, Index 30), Reel 20, Side 2, Index 30 (Reel 20)
  - Special Projects Re Stephen Duggan Memorial Lectures - 1951 (Reel 25, Side 1, Index 18), Reel 25, Side 1, Index 18 (Reel 25)
  - Special Projects - General - Lecturer Leaflets - 1951-52 (Reel 21, Side 2, Index 34), Reel 21, Side 2, Index 34 (Reel 21)
  - General - Special Projects - Lecturers - 1953-54 (Reel 21, Side 1, Index 5), Reel 21, Side 1, Index 5 (Reel 21)
  - Special Projects - Future Lecturer - John Macmurray - Britain - 1948-52 (Reel 21, Side 2, Index 21), Reel 21, Side 2, Index 21 (Reel 21)
  - Special Projects - Future Lecturers - Possible Distinguished Persons - 1948-55 (Reel 21, Side 2, Index 22), Reel 21, Side 2, Index 22 (Reel 21)
  - Special Projects - Future Lecturer - Charles Malik - Unsuccessful Lebanon - 1949 (Reel 21, Side 2, Index 23), Reel 21, Side 2, Index 23 (Reel 21)
  - Special Projects - Future Lecturer - Maurice Schumann - France - 1949-52 (Reel 21, Side 2, Index 28), Reel 21, Side 2, Index 28 (Reel 21)
  - Special Projects - Future Lecturer - Sir John Maud - England - 1949-53 (Reel 21, Side 2, Index 29), Reel 21, Side 2, Index 29 (Reel 21)
  - Special Projects - Future Lecturers - India - 1949-53 (Reel 21, Side 2, Index 30), Reel 21, Side 2, Index 30 (Reel 21)
  - Special Projects - Future Lecturers - Japan - 1950 (Reel 21, Side 2, Index 32), Reel 21, Side 2, Index 32 (Reel 21)
  - Special Projects - Future Lecturer - Andre Sigfried - France - 1951 (Reel 21, Side 2, Index 33), Reel 21, Side 2, Index 33 (Reel 21)
  - Special Projects - Future Lecturers - Scandinavia - 1951-52 (Reel 21, Side 2, Index 35), Reel 21, Side 2, Index 35 (Reel 21)
  - General - Special Projects - Dr. Sharma - Future Lecturer - 1951-52 (Reel 20, Side 2, Index 31), Reel 20, Side 2, Index 31 (Reel 20)
  - Special Projects - Future Lecturer - Anthony Wedgwood Benn, M.P. Britain - 1951-1954 (Reel 21, Side 2, Index 36), Reel 21, Side 2, Index 36 (Reel 21)
  - Special Projects - Future Lecturer - S.R. Shafaq - Iran - 1952 (Reel 21, Side 2, Index 37), Reel 21, Side 2, Index 37 (Reel 21)
  - General - Special Projects - Zakir Husain - Future Lecturer - Unsuccessful - 1952 (Reel 21, Side 1, Index 3), Reel 21, Side 1, Index 3 (Reel 21)
  - Special Projects - Future Lecturer - Sr. Manuel De La Sierra - Spain - 1952 (Reel 21, Side 2, Index 38), Reel 21, Side 2, Index 38 (Reel 21)
  - Special Projects - Future Lecturers and Policy Memos - 1952-53 (Reel 21, Side 2, Index 39), Reel 21, Side 2, Index 39 (Reel 21)
  - Special Projects - Future Lecturer - Raja Rao - India - 1953 (Reel 21, Side 2, Index 40), Reel 21, Side 2, Index 40 (Reel 21)
  - Special Projects - Future Lecturer - Pierre Olivier Lapie - France - 1953 (Reel 21, Side 2, Index 41), Reel 21, Side 2, Index 41 (Reel 21)
  - Special Projects - Future Lecturer - Eli Prins - Britain - 1953 (Reel 21, Side 2, Index 42), Reel 21, Side 2, Index 42 (Reel 21)
  - Special Projects - Future Lecturer - Francois Goguel - France - 1953 (Reel 21, Side 2, Index 43), Reel 21, Side 2, Index 43 (Reel 21)
  - Special Projects - Future Lecturer - Dr. Eugene Gerstenmaier - Germany - 1953 (Reel 21, Side 2, Index 44), Reel 21, Side 2, Index 44 (Reel 21)
  - Special Projects - Future Lecturer - Prince Dhani - Thailand - 1953 (Reel 21, Side 2, Index 45), Reel 21, Side 2, Index 45 (Reel 21)
  - Special Projects - Future Lecturer - Robert B. Durrant - South Africa - 1953 (Reel 21, Side 2, Index 46), Reel 21, Side 2, Index 46 (Reel 21)
  - Special Projects - Future Lecturer - Dr. Vasco Hariz - Argentina (Brazil) - 1953 (Reel 21, Side 2, Index 47), Reel 21, Side 2, Index 47 (Reel 21)
  - Special Projects - Future Lecturer - Dr. P.E. Dustoor - India - 1953-54 (Reel 21, Side 2, Index 48), Reel 21, Side 2, Index 48 (Reel 21)
  - Special Projects - Future Lecturer - Marquis Paolo Misciatelli - Italy - 1954 (Reel 21, Side 2, Index 49), Reel 21, Side 2, Index 49 (Reel 21)
  - Special Projects - Future Lecturer - Mr. R.N. Lindsay - Britain - 1954 (Reel 21, Side 2, Index 50), Reel 21, Side 2, Index 50 (Reel 21)
  - Special Projects - Future Lecturers - Italian-American Exchange Program - 1954 (Reel 21, Side 2, Index 51), Reel 21, Side 2, Index 51 (Reel 21)
  - Special Projects - Future Lecturers - France - 1954 (Reel 21, Side 2, Index 52), Reel 21, Side 2, Index 52 (Reel 21)
  - Special Projects - Future Lecturer - Dr. Paul L. Dengler - Austria - 1954, 1951-52 (Reel 21, Side 2, Index 54), Reel 21, Side 2, Index 54 (Reel 21)
  - Special Projects - Future Lecturer - H.A. Schwarz-Liebermann - Germany - 1954 (Reel 21, Side 2, Index 55), Reel 21, Side 2, Index 55 (Reel 21)
  - Special Projects - Future Lecturers - Mr. Eric Gillett - Britain - 1954-55 (Reel 21, Side 2, Index 56), Reel 21, Side 2, Index 56 (Reel 21)
  - Special Projects - Future Lecturers - Mr. Robin Darwin - Britain - 1954-55 (Reel 21, Side 2, Index 57), Reel 21, Side 2, Index 57 (Reel 21)
  - Special Projects - Future Lecturers - Mrs. Suzanna Ostbye - 1955 (Reel 21, Side 2, Index 59), Reel 21, Side 2, Index 59 (Reel 21)
  - Special Projects - Future Lecturer - Liucien De Sainte Lourette - France - 1955 (Reel 21, Side 2, Index 62), Reel 21, Side 2, Index 62 (Reel 21)
  - Special Projects - Future Lecturers - Dr. German Arcinegas - Colombia - 1956 (Reel 21, Side 2, Index 63), Reel 21, Side 2, Index 63 (Reel 21)
  - Special Projects - Future Lecturers - Professor F. Chiappelli - Switzerland - 1956 (Reel 21, Side 2, Index 64), Reel 21, Side 2, Index 64 (Reel 21)
  - Special Projects - Future Lecturers -J.A. Ayala -El Salvador - Jack Ashley - Britain - 1955-56 (Reel 21, Side 2, Index 65), Reel 21, Side 2, Index 65 (Reel 21)
  - Special Projects - Future Lecturers - Mr. S. Bugge-Norway - Mr. Balasundaram-India - M.G. Blanco-Spain - R. Brudman-Belgium - 1955-56 (Reel 21, Side 2, Index 66), Reel 21, Side 2, Index 66 (Reel 21)
  - Special Projects - Future Lecturers - Mr. Naresh Chandra - India - Mr. Kenneth M. Clark - Britain - 1955-56 (Reel 21, Side 2, Index 67), Reel 21, Side 2, Index 67 (Reel 21)
  - Special Projects - Future Lecturers - D - 1954-55 (Reel 21, Side 2, Index 68), Reel 21, Side 2, Index 68 (Reel 21)
  - Special Projects - Future Lecturers - E - 1954-55 (Reel 21, Side 2, Index 69), Reel 21, Side 2, Index 69 (Reel 21)
  - Special Projects - Future Lecturers - F - 1955-56 (Reel 21, Side 2, Index 70), Reel 21, Side 2, Index 70 (Reel 21)
  - Special Projects - Future Lecturers - G - 1952-1956 (Reel 21, Side 2, Index 71), Reel 21, Side 2, Index 71 (Reel 21)
  - Special Projects - Future Lecturers - H - 1952-1956 (Reel 21, Side 2, Index 72), Reel 21, Side 2, Index 72 (Reel 21)
  - Special Projects - Future Lecturers - I - 1952-1955 (Reel 21, Side 2, Index 73), Reel 21, Side 2, Index 73 (Reel 21)
  - Special Projects - Future Lecturers - J - 1956 (Reel 21, Side 2, Index 74), Reel 21, Side 2, Index 74 (Reel 21)
  - Special Projects - Future Lecturers - K - 1954-55 (Reel 21, Side 2, Index 75), Reel 21, Side 2, Index 75 (Reel 21)
  - Special Projects - Future Lecturers - L - 1953-54 (Reel 21, Side 2, Index 76), Reel 21, Side 2, Index 76 (Reel 21)
  - Special Projects - Future Lecturers - M - 1953-1956 (Reel 21, Side 2, Index 77), Reel 21, Side 2, Index 77 (Reel 21)
  - Special Projects - Future Lecturers - N - 1947-1954 (Reel 22, Side 1, Index 1), Reel 22, Side 1, Index 1 (Reel 22)
  - Special Projects - Future Lecturers - O - 1953-1954 (Reel 22, Side 1, Index 2), Reel 22, Side 1, Index 2 (Reel 22)
  - Special Projects - Future Lecturers - P-Q - 1952-1956 (Reel 22, Side 1, Index 3), Reel 22, Side 1, Index 3 (Reel 22)
  - Special Projects - Future Lecturers - R - 1955-1956 (Reel 22, Side 1, Index 4), Reel 22, Side 1, Index 4 (Reel 22)
  - Special Projects - Future Lecturers - S - 1955-1956 (Reel 22, Side 1, Index 5), Reel 22, Side 1, Index 5 (Reel 22)
  - Special Projects - Future Lecturers - T-U - 1952-1955 (Reel 22, Side 1, Index 6), Reel 22, Side 1, Index 6 (Reel 22)
  - Special Projects - Future Lecturers - V - 1953-1954 (Reel 22, Side 1, Index 7), Reel 22, Side 1, Index 7 (Reel 22)
  - Special Projects - Future Lecturers - W - 1954-1955 (Reel 22, Side 1, Index 8), Reel 22, Side 1, Index 8 (Reel 22)
  - Special Projects - Future Lecturers - Z - 1955 (Reel 22, Side 1, Index 9), Reel 22, Side 1, Index 9 (Reel 22)
  - Malaysia - Selection Committee Scholarships - Visitors - Fullbright Information - 1948-50 (Reel 19, Side 1, Index 18), Reel 19, Side 1, Index 18 (Reel 19)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene - 1931 (Reel 3, Side 2, Index 18), Reel 3, Side 2, Index 18 (Reel 3)
  - Near East College Association - 1942 (Reel 12, Side 2, Index 35), Reel 12, Side 2, Index 35 (Reel 12)
  - Near East College Association - 1943 (Reel 14, Side 4, Index 4), Reel 14, Side 4, Index 4 (Reel 14)
  - Near East - 1944 (Reel 13, Side 1, Index 38), Reel 13, Side 1, Index 38 (Reel 13)
  - Near East College Association - 1946 (Reel 15, Side 2, Index 25), Reel 15, Side 2, Index 25 (Reel 15)
  - National Education Association - Agreement No. 2 with IIE - Report of Agreement No. 1 - 1948-49, 1951 (Reel 20, Side 2, Index 21), Reel 20, Side 2, Index 21 (Reel 20)
  - National Catholic Welfare Conference Austrian Program - 1948-51 (Reel 20, Side 1, Index 6), Reel 20, Side 1, Index 6 (Reel 20)
  - General - National Catholic Welfare Conference - Fellowship Grants - 1948-53 (Reel 19, Side 2, Index 22), Reel 19, Side 2, Index 22 (Reel 19)
  - NAFSA - Training Committee Surveys - 1950 (Reel 19, Side 2, Index 17), Reel 19, Side 2, Index 17 (Reel 19)
  - National Educational Association - Dr. William G. Carr - General - 1950-51 (Reel 20, Side 2, Index 20), Reel 20, Side 2, Index 20 (Reel 20)
  - National Education Association - Transfer of Funds from Norway - 1951-55 (Reel 25, Side 1, Index 22), Reel 25, Side 1, Index 22 (Reel 25)
  - National Education Association - Korean Program - 1951-55 (Reel 25, Side 1, Index 23), Reel 25, Side 1, Index 23 (Reel 25)
  - National Education Association - General - 1951-1955 (Reel 25, Side 1, Index 24), Reel 25, Side 1, Index 24 (Reel 25)
  - Special Projects - Holland - 1931 - Dr. J.J.L. Duynendak (Reel 8, Side 1, Index 9), Reel 8, Side 1, Index 9 (Reel 8)
  - Netherlands - 1933 (Reel 4, Side 2, Index 3), Reel 4, Side 2, Index 3 (Reel 4)
  - Netherlands - Netherland-America Foundation - 1935 (Reel 5, Side 1, Index 14), Reel 5, Side 1, Index 14 (Reel 5)
  - Netherlands - Holland - 1943 (Reel 13, Side 2, Index 33), Reel 13, Side 2, Index 33 (Reel 13)
  - Netherlands - Netherland-America Society - 1943 (Reel 14, Side 1, Index 5), Reel 14, Side 1, Index 5 (Reel 14)
  - Netherlands - Holland - 1944, 1946 (Reel 14, Side 1, Index 22), Reel 14, Side 1, Index 22 (Reel 14)
  - Netherlands - Netherland-America Foundation - 1945 (Reel 15, Side 1, Index 24), Reel 15, Side 1, Index 24 (Reel 15)
  - Netherlands - Student Exchange Netherlands Embassy - Washington Correspondence - 1945-49 (Reel 29, Side 2, Index 31), Reel 29, Side 2, Index 31 (Reel 29)
  - Netherlands - Holland - 1946 (Reel 14, Side 2, Index 28), Reel 14, Side 2, Index 28 (Reel 14)
  - Netherlands - Holland - Ministry of Education - 1946 (Reel 15, Side 1, Index 42), Reel 15, Side 1, Index 42 (Reel 15)
  - Netherlands - Shell Chemical Corporation Fellowships - 1946-1949 (Reel 16, Side 2, Index 29), Reel 16, Side 2, Index 29 (Reel 16)
  - Netherlands - Ministry of Education - 1947-48 (Reel 16, Side 2, Index 30), Reel 16, Side 2, Index 30 (Reel 16)
  - Netherlands - Netherland-America Foundation - 1947 (Reel 30, Side 1, Index 2), Reel 30, Side 1, Index 2 (Reel 30)
  - Netherlands - Letter to Selection Committee - 1948 (Reel 16, Side 2, Index 28), Reel 16, Side 2, Index 28 (Reel 16)
  - Netherlands - Student Exchange - Annual Letter to Selection Committee - 1948-1953 (Reel 29, Side 2, Index 36), Reel 29, Side 2, Index 36 (Reel 29)
  - Netherlands - Student Exchange - Netherland-America Institute Correspondence - 1949 (Reel 29, Side 2, Index 32), Reel 29, Side 2, Index 32 (Reel 29)
  - Netherlands - Dutch Student Fund - 1949 (Reel 17, Side 1, Index 22), Reel 17, Side 1, Index 22 (Reel 17)
  - Netherlands - Correspondence with Embassy, Washington D.C. - 1949-50-51 (Reel 19, Side 2, Index 28), Reel 19, Side 2, Index 28 (Reel 19)
  - Netherlands - Correspondence with Embassy- Ministry of Education, The Hague - 1949-50 (Reel 19, Side 2, Index 29), Reel 19, Side 2, Index 29 (Reel 19)
  - Netherlands - Fullbright Travel Grant Program - 1949-50 (Reel 20, Side 1, Index 12), Reel 20, Side 1, Index 12 (Reel 20)
  - Netherlands - 1950 (Reel 19, Side 2, Index 30), Reel 19, Side 2, Index 30 (Reel 19)
  - Netherlands - Selection Committee - Netherland-America Institute - Correspondence - 1950-51 - 1950 (Reel 29, Side 2, Index 37), Reel 29, Side 2, Index 37 (Reel 29)
  - Netherlands - Selection Committee - Netherland-America Institute - Correspondence - 1951-52 - 1951 (Reel 29, Side 2, Index 38), Reel 29, Side 2, Index 38 (Reel 29)
  - Netherlands - Department of State (IES) Memos - 1951-52 - 1951 (Reel 29, Side 2, Index 39), Reel 29, Side 2, Index 39 (Reel 29)
  - Netherlands - Selection Committee - Correspondence - 1952-53 - 1952 (Reel 29, Side 2, Index 35), Reel 29, Side 2, Index 35 (Reel 29)
  - Netherlands - Selection Committee - Correspondence - 1953-54 - 1952-53 (Reel 29, Side 2, Index 33), Reel 29, Side 2, Index 33 (Reel 29)
  - Netherlands - Department of State (IES) Correspondence - 1953-54 - 1953 (Reel 29, Side 2, Index 40), Reel 29, Side 2, Index 40 (Reel 29)
  - Netherlands - Student Exchange - Annual Letter - 1953 (Reel 29, Side 2, Index 34), Reel 29, Side 2, Index 34 (Reel 29)
  - Netherlands - General - Dr. Kwast's Trip - 1953 (Reel 30, Side 1, Index 1), Reel 30, Side 1, Index 1 (Reel 30)
  - Netherlands - Netherland-America Foundation - 1954 (Reel 30, Side 1, Index 3), Reel 30, Side 1, Index 3 (Reel 30)
  - Netherlands - Selection Committee - Correspondence - 1955-56 - 1955 (Reel 29, Side 2, Index 41), Reel 29, Side 2, Index 41 (Reel 29)
  - Netherlands - Department of State (IES) Correspondence - 1955-56 - 1955 (Reel 29, Side 2, Index 42), Reel 29, Side 2, Index 42 (Reel 29)
  - Netherlands - Selection Committee - Correspondence - 1956-57 - 1956 (Reel 33, Side 2, Index 22), Reel 33, Side 2, Index 22 (Reel 33)
  - Netherlands - Department of State (IES) Correspondence - 1956-57 - 1956 (Reel 33, Side 2, Index 21), Reel 33, Side 2, Index 21 (Reel 33)
  - Netherlands - Netherland-America Foundation - Correspondence - 1956-57 (Reel 30, Side 1, Index 4), Reel 30, Side 1, Index 4 (Reel 30)
  - Netherlands - Selection Committee - Netherland-America Institutute - Correspondence - 1957-58 - 1957 (Reel 29, Side 2, Index 43), Reel 29, Side 2, Index 43 (Reel 29)
  - Netherlands - Department of State (IES) Correspondence - 1957-58 - 1957 (Reel 29, Side 2, Index 44), Reel 29, Side 2, Index 44 (Reel 29)
  - Norway - Special Projects - Dr. Edward Hambro - 1939 (Reel 21, Side 1, Index 18), Reel 21, Side 1, Index 18 (Reel 21)
  - Norway - Special Projects - Dr. Edward I. Hambro - 1940 (Reel 21, Side 2, Index 8), Reel 21, Side 2, Index 8 (Reel 21)
  - Norway - Re Student Exchange - America Committee-Oslo Royal Norwegian Information Services - Department of State - 1946 (Reel 27, Side 1, Index 18), Reel 27, Side 1, Index 18 (Reel 27)
  - Norway - General - Student Exchange - Mr. Knut Erik Tranoy - 1946-47 (Reel 14, Side 2, Index 24), Reel 14, Side 2, Index 24 (Reel 14)
  - Norway - Selection Committee Norway- America Association Correspondence - 1951-52, 1952-53 - 1950-51 (Reel 30, Side 1, Index 12), Reel 30, Side 1, Index 12 (Reel 30)
  - Norway - Department of State (IES) Correspondence - 1952-53 - 1952 (Reel 30, Side 1, Index 13), Reel 30, Side 1, Index 13 (Reel 30)
  - Norway - Selection Committee Norway- America Association Correspondence - 1953-54 - 1953 (Reel 30, Side 1, Index 10), Reel 30, Side 1, Index 10 (Reel 30)
  - Norway - Department of State (IES) Correspondence - 1953-54 - 1953 (Reel 30, Side 1, Index 11), Reel 30, Side 1, Index 11 (Reel 30)
  - Norway - University of Oslo - Summer School - 1953-1958 (Reel 32, Side 1, Index 6), Reel 32, Side 1, Index 6 (Reel 32)
  - Norway - Selection Committee Norway- America Association Correspondence - 1955-56 - 1955 (Reel 30, Side 1, Index 14), Reel 30, Side 1, Index 14 (Reel 30)
  - Norway - Department of State (IES) Correspondence - 1955-56 - 1955 (Reel 30, Side 1, Index 15), Reel 30, Side 1, Index 15 (Reel 30)
  - Norway - Selection Committee Norway- America Association Correspondence - 1957-58 - 1957 (Reel 30, Side 1, Index 16), Reel 30, Side 1, Index 16 (Reel 30)
  - Norway - Department of State (IES) Correspondence - 1957-58 - 1957 (Reel 30, Side 1, Index 17), Reel 30, Side 1, Index 17 (Reel 30)
  - Phillipines - A-Z (Reel 11, Side 2, Index 29), Reel 11, Side 2, Index 29 (Reel 11)
  - Palestine - 1935 (Reel 4, Side 2, Index 21), Reel 4, Side 2, Index 21 (Reel 4)
  - Persia - General - 1936 (Reel 7, Side 2, Index 19), Reel 7, Side 2, Index 19 (Reel 7)
  - Phillipines - 1944 (Reel 13, Side 1, Index 39), Reel 13, Side 1, Index 39 (Reel 13)
  - Portugal - Department of State - 1944 (Reel 13, Side 1, Index 40), Reel 13, Side 1, Index 40 (Reel 13)
  - Puerto Rico - 1944 (Reel 13, Side 1, Index 41), Reel 13, Side 1, Index 41 (Reel 13)
  - Poland 1934 (Reel 11, Side 1, Index 33), Reel 11, Side 1, Index 33 (Reel 11)
  - Poland 1935 (Reel 11, Side 2, Index 30), Reel 11, Side 2, Index 30 (Reel 11)
  - Poland Special Projects Dr. Stephan Przeworski (Reel 21, Side 1, Index 19), Reel 21, Side 1, Index 19 (Reel 21)
  - Poland Special Projects A-Z 1940 (Reel 21, Side 2, Index 9), Reel 21, Side 2, Index 9 (Reel 21)
  - Poland 1943 (Reel 13, Side 2, Index 35), Reel 13, Side 2, Index 35 (Reel 13)
  - Poland 1946 (Reel 14, Side 2, Index 26), Reel 14, Side 2, Index 26 (Reel 14)
  - Rumania - 1944 (Reel 13, Side 1, Index 42), Reel 13, Side 1, Index 42 (Reel 13)
  - Refugees Fellowships for Refugess 1939 (Reel 16, Side 1, Index 21), Reel 16, Side 1, Index 21 (Reel 16)
  - Refugees General 1943 (Reel 13, Side 1, Index 9), Reel 13, Side 1, Index 9 (Reel 13)
  - Refugee Scholar Fund Clearance Committee Memos for the Staff Section 1943-1944 (Reel 16, Side 1, Index 23), Reel 16, Side 1, Index 23 (Reel 16)
  - Refugee Scholar Fund Miscellaneous, Memos, etc. 1943-1945 (Reel 16, Side 1, Index 20), Reel 16, Side 1, Index 20 (Reel 16)
  - General Refugees 1944 (Reel 16, Side 2, Index 11), Reel 16, Side 2, Index 11 (Reel 16)
  - General Refugees 1944 (Reel 16, Side 1, Index 22), Reel 16, Side 1, Index 22 (Reel 16)
  - General - Refugees American Committee for Refugee Scholars, Writers, and Artists 1945 (Reel 14, Side 1, Index 14), Reel 14, Side 1, Index 14 (Reel 14)
  - Refugees General American Committee for migr Scholars, Writers and Artists 1946 (Reel 14, Side 2, Index 8), Reel 14, Side 2, Index 8 (Reel 14)
  - General Refugees American Committee for migr Scholars, Writers, and Artists 1947 (Reel 16, Side 1, Index 14), Reel 16, Side 1, Index 14 (Reel 16)
  - Russia 1929-1931 (Reel 10, Side 2, Index 52), Reel 10, Side 2, Index 52 (Reel 10)
  - Special Projects Russia 1931 (Reel 8, Side 1, Index 12), Reel 8, Side 1, Index 12 (Reel 8)
  - Russia 1932 (Reel 11, Side 1, Index 1), Reel 11, Side 1, Index 1 (Reel 11)
  - Russia Moscow Summer School Early Negotiaions (1934 Session) 1932-1934 (Reel 10, Side 2, Index 10), Reel 10, Side 2, Index 10 (Reel 10)
  - Russia Anglo-American Institute RE: Moscow Summer School 1933-1934 (Reel 17, Side 2, Index 12), Reel 17, Side 2, Index 12 (Reel 17)
  - Russia Moscow University Summer Session -Anglo American Institute Advisory Committee - Minutes 1934 (Reel 10, Side 2, Index 4), Reel 10, Side 2, Index 4 (Reel 10)
  - Russia Moscow University Summer Session -Announcements, Instructions, Etc .1934 (Reel 11, Side 1, Index 31), Reel 11, Side 1, Index 31 (Reel 11)
  - Russia Moscow Summer School Session 1934 (Reel 11, Side 1, Index 32), Reel 11, Side 1, Index 32 (Reel 11)
  - Russia 1935 (Reel 11, Side 2, Index 31), Reel 11, Side 2, Index 31 (Reel 11)
  - Russia - RE - Russian Summer School and Correspondence with Mr. Lamont 1938 (Reel 7, Side 2, Index 45), Reel 7, Side 2, Index 45 (Reel 7)
  - Russian Refugees Tolstoy Foundation 1939 (Reel 9, Side 1, Index 20), Reel 9, Side 1, Index 20 (Reel 9)
  - Russia Russian Student Fund Stephen Duggan 1942 (Reel 12, Side 1, Index 11), Reel 12, Side 1, Index 11 (Reel 12)
  - Russia 1944 (Reel 13, Side 1, Index 43), Reel 13, Side 1, Index 43 (Reel 13)